Now the thing about
like going after like
five or 10 more
ways to be able
to load up your
fundraising odds of success
is that it gives
the confidence If
the only has one
VC who's showing interest
they're like everything is
on this one VC
Yeah it's like super
tunnel vision Super tunnel
vision desperate Yes Like
live or die kind
situation Yes And then
the interaction between that
then the VC will
be like hey is
this founder actually do
people actually want this
Do market forces support
the success of this
company Yeah They may
not say that oh
I smell desperation I
should go away It's
not like that It's
more like they see
that and then they
get a that if
I'm the only one
backing it the founder
is not gonna have
enough money to build
a big business Yeah
And even though I
have full conviction if
nobody else has conviction
down the line like
this is you see
customers and and whatever
all in line makes
you yeah sure Okay
that's human psychology right
Like people wanna be
where there's buzz So
if we get curious
about why it is
we have less leverage
in that moment and
we go deeper into
that and say let's
kind of like get
the let's kind of
load up let's load
up our cards in
our favor odds in
our favor